It won't be long now.
现在不会很久了。
Structural integrity has passed the point of no return.
结构完整性已经过了无可挽回的地步。
I just need to put in the final calculations.
我只需要把最后的计算放进去。
There has to be another way.
肯定还有其他办法。
This is the only way.
这是唯一的办法。
My son, someday I pray you'll have a child
我的孩子，有一天我祈祷你会有一个孩子
that will bring you as much joy as you have brought us.
这将给你带来和你给我们带来的一样多的joy。
Even in this short time, you have changed our lives for the better.
即使在这么短的时间里，你们也让我们的生活变得更好。
We love you with all that we are.
我们全心全意地爱你。
Goodbye, my son.
再见，我的儿子。
It is time.
是时候了。
Trans-light engines activated in three, two, one.
超光速引擎启动，倒计时三，二，一。
"In the decade of the 1930s,
“在20世纪30年代的十年里，
even the great city of Metropolis was not spared
即使是大都会也未能幸免
the ravages of worldwide depression.
世界性大萧条的蹂躏。
In the times of fear and confusion, the job of informing the public
在恐惧和困惑的时代，告知公众的工作
was the responsibility of the daily planet."
是《星球日报》的责任所在。
Somebody kill me.
谁来杀了我。
Why couldn't you guys be, I don't know, like, doctors or lawyers,
为什么你们不能，我不知道，像是医生或律师，
or, like, a celebrity chef?
或者，就像，一个名厨？
Yeah, like, anything besides reporters.
是的，就像，除了记者以外的任何事情。
Because reporting is an important and essential part of a civilized society.
因为报道是文明社会的重要和必不可少的一部分。
They call it the fifth branch of government.
他们称它为政府的第五个分支。
Or is it the fourth? Do you know where my purse is?
还是说是第四次？你知道我的钱包在哪里吗？
The couch.
沙发。
But, okay, doing a report on reporters, it's boring.
但是，好吧，做一份关于记者的报道，很无聊。
Bodng?
伯丁？
Good reporters make good stories.
好的记者会写出好的故事。
Boring reporters don't last long.
无聊的记者不会持续很长时间。
Listen, every time I start a story, I follow a couple of rules.
听着，每次我开始一个故事，我都会遵守几条规则。
One, find your hook, your angle.
第一，找到你的钩子，你的角度。
How can you write this thing like no one else? It's like...
你怎么能写出独一无二的东西呢？就像是..。
It's like, you know those violent video games you play?
就像，你知道你玩的那些暴力电子游戏吗？
I mean, iwouldn't call them violent.
我是说，我不会说他们是暴力的。
Trust me, they're violent.
相信我，他们很暴力。
In those games, you're always looking for the weak point, right?
在那些游戏中，你总是在寻找弱点，对吗？
And sometimes, you have to hit them with different moves,
有时，你必须用不同的动作来打击他们，
in different locations to beat it.
在不同的地方打败它。
Same thing with reporting.
报道也是如此。
Find your angle, your "in"
找到你的角度，你的“入”
and you'll vanquish your report in no time.
你很快就能完成你的报告。
I guess.
我想是的。
Hey, which one of us has won journalist of the year?
嘿，我们谁获得了年度最佳记者奖？
You or me?
你还是我？
Oh, and one more thing.
哦，还有一件事。
With most stories, we already know the ending.
对于大多数故事，我们已经知道了结局。
The airliner crashed. The girl was saved.
客机坠毁了。女孩得救了。
What's interesting is how that happened.
有趣的是这是如何发生的。
How we got there.
我们是怎么到那里的。
Always start at the beginning, and you'll already have your end.
总是从头开始，你就已经有了终点。
The rest is cake.
剩下的都是小菜一碟。
Speaking of which, I have to pick up the birthday cake by 5:00. Shoot.
说到这里，我必须在5点前拿到生日蛋糕。开枪吧。
You want me to write about how you two dated?
你想让我写你们两个是怎么约会的？
I love you, mom, I love you.
我爱你，妈妈，我爱你。
But you and dad are the most unexciting couple in the entire universe
但你和爸爸是整个宇宙中最乏味的一对
If only that were true.
如果这是真的就好了。
Uh, that's hairspray. Your water bottle's by the door.
呃，那是发胶。你的水瓶在门边。
Yeah, I'll probably need it.
是啊，我可能会需要它。
Remember, do your best.
记住，要全力以赴。
I have to head to the city, but I'll be back before dinner.
我得进城了，但晚饭前我会回来的。
Your dad should be home soon.
你爸爸应该很快就会回家了。
Love you.
爱你。
- Three, two... - Forgot the purse.
-三，二……-忘了带钱包。
And, Jonathan...
还有乔纳森。
No looking for birthday presents while I'm gone.
我不在的时候，不要找生日礼物。
Mm-hmm.
嗯-嗯。
Fine.
很好。
Bingo!
对啰!
Cosplay?
角色扮演？
Oh, too easy.
哦，太容易了。
Don't look inside, Jon. You don't want to ruin the surprise.
别往里面看，乔恩。你不会想毁了惊喜吧。
- But then again... - Jonathan!
-但话又说回来...-乔纳森！
Dad's home.
爸爸回来了。
- Hey, kiddo. - Hey, how was your trip?
-嘿，孩子.-嘿，你的旅行怎么样？
Good. Interesting.
好的。有意思的。
The scientists have discovered this strange phenomenon
科学家们发现了这种奇怪的现象
with certain types of ants.
与某些类型的蚂蚁。
Normally, they follow the queen ant's directions,
正常情况下，它们遵循蚁后的指示，
but now, they're moving of their own accord.
但现在，他们正在主动行动。
Which is better than if the queen ant was dead,
这比蚂蚁后死了要好，
because if the queen ant dies, then so does the colony.
因为如果蚁后死了，那么蚁群也会死。
Sounds amazing.
听起来很棒。
Sorry I'm boring you with nerd talk.
抱歉，我用书呆子的话烦到你了。
Now, if you're done looking for presents in the house...
现在，如果你在房子里找完礼物了.
What? Me? No, I would never.
什么？我?不，我永远不会。
How about you help me with a few of the chores
你能帮我做几件家务吗？
that seem to have been neglected while I was away?
在我不在的时候似乎被忽视了？
Hey.
嘿。
Now you've done it!
现在你做到了！
Come here.
到这儿来。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Hmm.
嗯。
Where could he be?
他会在哪里呢？
-Gotcha! {933931
-明白了！{933931
- Dad? - Yeah?
-爸爸？-什么事？
I know that you and mom think that your job is super important,
我知道你和妈妈认为你的工作非常重要，
and it is, and everything, but I don't know.
是的，还有所有的事情，但我不知道。
I... I miss having you around.
我..。我怀念有你在身边的日子。
Yeah, I miss being around.
是啊，我很怀念在身边的日子。
Son, someday, this will make sense,
儿子，总有一天，这会有意义的，
but being a reporter, it's a big responsibility.
但作为一名记者，这是一项重大的责任。
- It's... - The fourth estate.
-这是...--第四产业。
Yeah, yeah. Mom gave me the whole spiel.
是啊，是啊。妈妈把整个故事都给我讲了。
It sounds like fake news to me.
对我来说，这听起来像假新闻。
I mean, you've been gone for two weeks, for what?
我是说，你已经离开两个星期了，为了什么？
Just to find out why ants are going crazy?
就为了找出为什么蚂蚁会发疯？
Well, it's really fascinating. They actually...
嗯，这真的很吸引人。他们实际上..。
Yeah, I'm sure. I just...
是啊，我确定。我只是.。
Couldn't you, I don't know, look it up on the Internet?
你就不能，我不知道，上网查一下吗？
If I didn't have to go, I wouldn't.
如果我不一定要去，我就不会去了。
You need to believe me, son.
你要相信我，儿子。
Butjobs, especially mine, involve some sacrifice.
但工作，尤其是我的工作，需要做出一些牺牲。
Come on, it's not like you're putting your life on the line.
得了吧，你又不是在拿自己的性命冒险。
You're just putting your name on a byline.
你只是把你的名字写在署名上。
You'd be surprised.
你会大吃一惊的。
But you'll be here tomorrow, right?
但你明天会来的，对吧？
For your game?
为了你的比赛？
Or your birthday?
还是你的生日？
I thought maybe you forgot.
我还以为你忘了呢。
Jonathan, you are the most important thing that has ever happened to me.
乔纳森，你是我所经历过的最重要的事情。
I'll never forget about you.
我永远不会忘记你。
Wow! Look at that one!
哇!看那一只！
Yeah, that's... you know what, kid?
是的，那是..。你知道吗，孩子？
I think your mom just got back. You better wash up for dinner.
我想你妈妈刚回来。你最好去洗个澡去吃晚饭。
Uh, where are you going?
呃，你要去哪里？
I just realized I have a quick errand to run.
我刚意识到我有个急事要办。
Tell your mom I'll be back later.
告诉你妈妈我一会儿就回来。
- Sure. - And Jonathan...
-当然。-还有乔纳森...
Happy birthday.
生日快乐。
Thanks, dad.
谢谢你，爸爸。
Superman to watchtower. Everyone all right?
超人呼叫瞭望塔。大家都还好吗？
Everything's fine. We were hit by some sort of space debris.
一切都很好。我们被某种太空碎片击中了。
Looks like you closed it up,
看起来你把它关起来了，
- but if you want to come in... - No time.
-但如果你想进来...-没时间了
A Tsunami is about to hit Japan.
一场海啸即将袭击日本。
Contact Batman. Let him know the damage assessment.
联系蝙蝠侠。让他知道损失评估。
He's into that sort of thing.
他对这类事情很感兴趣。
And then there was one.
然后就有了一个。
Now batting, Jonathan Kent!
现在击球，乔纳森·肯特！
Yeah!
嗯!
Come on, Jon! You got this!
来吧，乔恩！你能行的！
Whoo!
喔！
Oh, look. It's can't hit Kent.
哦看啊。它打不中肯特。
We might as well start packing up and head home
我们不妨开始收拾行装回家吧
because this game's as good as over.
因为这场比赛差不多要结束了。
Strike one!
一振出局！
Strike two!
二振出局！
Come on, Jon, you got this.
加油，乔恩，你能行的。
Strike three, you're out!
三振出局，你出局了！
Good job, Jonathan can't!
干得好，乔纳森做不到！
You'll get them next time, kiddo.
下一次你会得到他们的，孩子。
Now, how about we go celebrate your birthday?
现在，我们去给你庆祝生日怎么样？
Jonathan?
乔纳森？
I just want to go home, mom.
我只想回家，妈妈。
How is he?
他怎么样了？
Upset.
心烦意乱。
You said you were gonna be there.
你说过你会去的。
- I know, but there was... - Hey, you don't need to tell me.
-我知道，但有...-嘿，你不需要告诉我.
Remember how many dates you had to leave in the middle of
还记得你中途留下了多少约会吗？
because of an "emergency"?
是因为“紧急情况”吗？
The world needs you, I get it.
世界需要你，我明白。
But... he needs you, too.
但是..。他也需要你。
- I know. - He's getting older.
-我知道.-他在变老。
Maybe... maybe it's time for the "talk."
也许.。也许是时候进行“谈话”了。
Jon? It's dad. Can I come in?
琼恩?我是爸爸。我能进来吗？
No!
不是的！
I know you're upset,
我知道你很难过，
- but work was... - Work is important.
-但工作是...-工作是重要的。
Yeah. You've told me.
嗯。你已经告诉过我了。
I just didn't think that it was more important than your word.
我只是不认为这比你的话更重要。
Look, I'm sorry.
听着，我很抱歉。
_i__ -i don't care that you're sorry.
_我__-我不在乎你是否抱歉。
I just want you to be here!
我只想让你留在这里！
You care more about your dumb job than you do your own son!
你关心你那份愚蠢的工作胜过关心你自己的儿子！
Jon, it's not like that.
乔恩，事情不是那样的。
Listen, let's talk this out.
听着，让我们谈谈这件事。
I'm coming in. Okay?
我要进去了。好吧?
Jonathan? Son?
乔纳森？儿子？
Leave me alone.
别管我。
I'm your father. I can't leave you alone.
我是你父亲。我不能丢下你一个人。
Sorry, kid, it's in the contract.
抱歉，孩子，这是合同上的。
No, seriously, dad. Something is... Something's wrong with me.
不，说真的，爸爸。有些事是..。我有点不对劲。
- I'm a freak. - No, you're not a freak.
-我是个怪胎.-不，你不是怪胎.
You're no more a freak than I am.
你和我一样不是怪胎
Dad, you just... You wouldn't understand.
爸爸，你只是..。你不会明白的。
Oh...
哦.。
I might.
我可能会的。
My dad is Superman?
我爸爸是超人？
Like, the Superman?
比如超人？
This is the best birthday ever!
这是有史以来最棒的生日！
Was it just the heat vision or was there something else?
是因为热视觉，还是有其他原因？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Does he have X-ray vision?
他有X光视力吗？
If he has X-ray vision, we can't send him to school.
如果他有X光视力，我们就不能送他去学校。
You know that, right?
你知道的，对吧？
I think it's just the heat vision.
我认为这只是火热的视觉。
You think? We need to know, Clark, this is serious.
你是这么想的吗？我们需要知道，克拉克，这是严肃的。
So that means that I'm a superhero, too, right?
所以这意味着我也是一个超级英雄，对吗？
Like, does that... does that mean I get to join the justice league and stuff?
就像，那是不是...这是不是意味着我可以加入正义联盟之类的组织？
Do I get to meet Batman?
我能见见蝙蝠侠吗？
What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办？
We knew this was a possibility. I just...
我们知道这是一种可能性。我只是.。
He wasn't lifting cars at two years old like you were.
他在两岁的时候不会像你那样举起汽车。
So, I thought maybe it skipped a generation, like, red hair.
所以，我想它可能跳过了一代人，比如，红发。
Don't worry, I'll get him checked out. We'll see what's happening.
别担心，我会给他做检查的。我们看看会发生什么。
It'll be fine.
一切都会好的。
Nope. Can't fly.
不是的。不会飞。
Mostly fine.
基本没问题。
Woo-hoo!
哇-呼！
Yeah!
嗯!
Woo-hoo!
哇-呼！
Oh, yeah!
哦，耶！
Whoa.
哇哦。
Yeah!
嗯!
Woo-hoo!
哇-呼！
Mom? Mom!
妈妈?妈妈!
What, honey?
怎么了，亲爱的？
Superman is out the window and he has some kid hanging on his back.
超人就在窗外，背上挂着几个孩子。
Yeah, you know what? I was wrong.
是啊，你知道吗？我错了。
Here's my phone. Have some fun.
这是我的手机。玩得开心点。
This is amazing!
这真是太棒了！
My favorite part of being an alien.
作为一个外星人我最喜欢的部分。
So, you're... okay. So...
所以，你是..。好吧。所以..。
That means that I'm half alien, too, right?
这意味着我也是半个外星人，对吗？
I'm half alien.
我是半个外星人。
I'm half alien!
我是半个外星人！
You're taking this a lot better than I thought you would.
你接受这件事比我想象的要好得多。
Why wouldn't I? I mean, this...
我怎么会不想呢？我是说，这..。
My dad is the greatest superhero in the world.
我爸爸是世界上最伟大的超级英雄。
Besides Batman.
除了蝙蝠侠。
It's pretty much the greatest birthday present ever.
这几乎是有史以来最棒的生日礼物了。
Yeah. It's been really hard not to tell you,
嗯。很难不告诉你，
but keeping you and your mother safe is my top priority.
但保护你和你母亲的安全是我的首要任务。
That means being on call.
这意味着随时待命。
My job, my real job is helping the world.
我的工作，我真正的工作是帮助世界。
Standing for truth, justice and the American way,
代表真理、正义和美国方式，
wherever that takes me.
无论它带我去哪里。
Awesome.
太棒了。
Sometimes. But as glamorous as you might think this is,
有时候。但是，尽管你可能认为这很迷人，
it takes me away from you and your mother.
这会让我远离你和你母亲。
And you should know it's dangerous.
你应该知道这很危险。
It's a real sacrifice.
这是一次真正的牺牲。
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
嗯，嗯，嗯。
Oh, what should I be called though?
哦，那我该叫什么呢？
What about... what about... Well, superboy's taken, right?
那..。那..。嗯，超人已经有人了，对吧？
So, what about, uh, dragoneyes, but with a "," z or supremo?
那么，那么，呃，龙眼，但有一个“，”z或最高领导人？
Or, uh, kid wonder!
或者，呃，小魔童！
Superman two or... Ugh! What's that smell?
超人2或..。啊！这是什么味儿？
Gotham city.
哥谭市。
This is Gotham?
这就是哥谭市？
I thought the Internet was exaggerating.
我觉得互联网太夸张了。
But why doesn't somebody do something about this?
但为什么没有人对此做点什么呢？
Somebody is.
有人是这样的。
Get him!
抓住他！
- Uh, dad, shouldn't we help him? - No.
-爸爸，我们不该帮他吗？-不.
He tends to get a bit grumpy when I step in.
当我插手时，他往往会变得有点暴躁。
Is he always this... oh!
他总是这么..。噢!
Rough? It's not as bad as it looks.
粗暴？情况并不像看起来那么糟糕。
He's actually going pretty easy on them.
实际上，他对他们的态度相当宽松。
That's easy?
这很容易吗？
This is my town, Batman.
这是我的小镇，蝙蝠侠。
Hey.
嘿。
Aw...
啊..。
Come on, Batman. Let's come to an agreement, huh?
来吧，蝙蝠侠。让我们达成协议，好吗？
I'll promise to be a good bird and you let me fly the Coop, eh?
我保证做一只好鸟，你让我飞，好吗？
Okay.
好吧。
No way!
不行!
Clark.
克拉克。
Hey, a little help here?
嘿，帮个忙好吗？
You... you... you're...
你.。你.。你是..。
I'm Batman.
我是蝙蝠侠。
Wow!
哇!
This is the... wow!
这是..。哇!
- This is the... - Welcome to the batcave.
-这是...-欢迎来到蝙蝠洞。
Look! That's the Batmobile,
看!那是蝙蝠车，
and the batcomputer,
和蝙蝠计算机，
and the batdinosaur. And that...
还有蝙蝠龙。而那..。
Who's the new kid? Obvious boy?
新来的孩子是谁？显而易见的男孩？
Jon, this is Batman's son, Damian.
乔恩，这是蝙蝠侠的儿子达米安。
Jon?
琼恩?
So, you have toilet powers?
所以，你有厕所的力量？
Relax, Damian. They're friends.
放松点，达米安。他们是朋友。
Sure. Friends.
好的。朋友。
So should I go into your utility belt and get the you-know-what-a-nite?
那我是不是应该到你的实用腰带里去买个你知道的夜宵？
Damian, please. They need our help.
达米安，拜托。他们需要我们的帮助。
Set up Jon in the meta analyzer.
在元分析器中设置Jon。
Don't you mean the bat meta analyzer?
你是说BAT元分析器吗？
Sorry. Sorry. I just thought... Never mind.
抱歉的。抱歉的。我只是想..。不要紧。
Fine. Follow me, farm boy.
很好。跟我来，农场男孩。
- Is that a giant penny? - Don't touch the penny.
-那是一个巨大的便士吗？-别碰那个便士.
In fact, don't touch anything.
事实上，什么都不要碰。
- Reminds me of us when we first met. - I was nicer.
-让我想起了我们第一次见面的时候。-我更友善。
How's he doing?
他怎么样了？
I mean, now that he's living with you.
我是说，现在他和你住在一起。
He wants to be good, I think.
我想，他想做个好人。
But what ra's and Talia put him through...
但是Ra和Talia让他经历的..。
Give it time.
给它点时间。
No one ever said parenting would be easy.
从来没有人说养育孩子是一件容易的事。
Especially when they've been through so much.
尤其是他们经历了这么多。
Thanks. I hope so.
谢谢。要是那样就好了。
- He's done. - Well?
-他完蛋了.-怎么了？
Nothing definitive.
没什么确定的。
I have no idea what powers could manifest next, if any at all.
我不知道下一步会有什么能力，如果真的有的话。
If his first power set was brought on by extreme stress,
如果他的第一套动力装置是由极端的压力引起的，
it stands to reason
言之有礼
that another traumatic moment...
又一个创伤性的时刻。
Might unlock something else.
可能会解锁其他东西。
Let's test that theory.
让我们来检验一下这一理论。
Damian!
达米安！
What was that? Are you kidding me?
那是什么？你在开我的玩笑吗？
- You piece of... - What?
-你这个……-什么？
You said a traumatic moment might help him unlock some more powers.
你说过创伤性的时刻可能会帮助他释放更多的力量。
Seems logical to test it out.
测试一下似乎是合乎逻辑的。
Not by trying to kill him.
而不是试图杀了他。
If I wanted to do that, he'd already be dead.
如果我想这么做，他早就死了。
That's enough.
足够了。
Who is this kid?
这孩子是谁？
Out. Now!
出去。现在!
Well, he's obviously not invulnerable.
他显然不是无懈可击的。
Obviously.
很明显。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
It's okay. He's had a tough time.
没关系的。他经历了一段艰难的时期。
He's had a tough time?
他经历了一段艰难的时光？
Jonathan, could I borrow your dad for a minute?
乔纳森，我能借你爸爸用一下吗？
Yeah. Oh, yeah, of course. Sure, sure, sure.
嗯。哦，是的，当然。当然，当然，当然。
I'll just be over here, you know, nursing my bat wounds.
我就在这里，你知道，护理我的蝙蝠伤口。
Have you heard from the watchtower lately?
你最近有瞭望塔的消息吗？
Green arrow hasn't checked in?
绿箭公司还没入住吗？
He said he'd give you updates after last night.
他说昨晚过后他会给你最新消息。
Last night?
昨晚?
The watchtower, it was knocked out of orbit.
瞭望塔，它被撞出了轨道。
I was able to right it before heading to Japan for the Tsunami.
我能够在前往日本参加海啸之前纠正它。
I told green arrow to check in with you, give updates.
我让绿箭向你汇报最新情况。
I haven't been able to raise them on comms.
我还没能通过通讯把他们养大。
I'm suspicious.
我很怀疑。
Well, that's not unusual for you.
这对你来说并不少见。
Try them again.
再试一次。
So, where should we meet for patrol?
那么，我们应该在哪里巡逻呢？
No patrol tonight.
今晚不巡逻了。
We've been called up to the watchtower for some emergency.
我们被叫到了瞭望塔，有紧急情况。
- Great. I'll head to the tower and... - Damian. Damian...
-太好了。我要去塔楼然后..。-达米安.达米安。
Only the titans have been called to the watchtower, and well...
只有巨人被召唤到了瞭望塔，而且……
You've never officially been inducted, so...
你还没有正式入伍过，所以...
An oversight, I'm sure.
我肯定，这是个疏忽。
I'll head over, swear on whatever you have handy and...
我会过去，用你手边的任何东西发誓...
No! No.
不是的！不是的。
Damian, we've taken a vote.
达米安，我们已经投票了。
We don't want you on the team.
我们不想让你加入我们的队伍。
You're just too violent,
你就是太暴力了，
and don't do well with others.
不要和别人相处得很好。
We are a team. We need to work as one,
我们是一个团队。我们需要团结一致，
and I'm sorry to say this,
我很抱歉这么说，
but you don't care for anyone but yourself.
但你不关心任何人，除了你自己。
- Sorry. - Sorry? Don't be sorry.
-对不起.-你说什么？不要抱歉。
The only reason I've come around
我来这里的唯一原因
is 'cause my father, Batman, begged me to.
是因为我父亲蝙蝠侠求我这么做。
And why would I want to hang out with a bunch of justice league wannabes anyway?
我为什么要和一群追求正义联盟的人混在一起呢？
- Damian, I'm just... - Good luck on failing without me.
-达米安，我只是...-祝你在没有我的情况下失败。
Hey, I was wondering if you could show me...
嘿，我在想你能不能给我看一下...
You have a cow?
你养了一头牛？
Of course I have a cow.
我当然有一头奶牛。
When was the last time you milked her?
你上次给她挤奶是什么时候？
Milked her?
给她挤奶？
Yeah. You have to milk it, it's a cow.
嗯。你得给它挤奶，它是头奶牛。
Listen, I can milk her, dude. It's fine, it's no problem.
听着，我可以给她挤奶，伙计。很好，没问题。
Over my dead body.
绝不允许。
I don't need some small town hick telling me how to take care of a cow.
我不需要小镇上的乡巴佬来教我怎么照顾一头牛。
I'm the grandson of the demon's head.
我是恶魔头颅的孙子。
I've killed more people than you'll ever meet.
我杀的人比你见过的都多。
So leave my cow and my cave alone!
所以离我的牛和我的洞穴远点！
Hey, don't look at me, he's your friend.
嘿，别看我，他是你的朋友。
Green arrow, is that you?
绿箭，是你吗？
Yes. Sorry.
是。抱歉的。
We 're having trouble with the comms.
我们的通讯出了点问题。
Whatever hit the watchtower, knocked out a couple of transmitters,
不管是什么击中了瞭望塔，摧毁了几个发射器，
but we're almost up and running.
但我们马上就要上线了。
Understood. Keep me updated as to your progress.
明白了。随时向我汇报你们的进展情况。
Of course, Batman. Watchtower out.
当然了，蝙蝠侠。瞭望塔完毕。
- Something's off. - Something's off.
-有点不对劲。-有点不对劲。
Let me drop Jonathan at home and we'll head to the watchtower,
让我把乔纳森放在家里，然后我们去瞭望塔，
see what's really going on.
看看到底是怎么回事。
Hey, dad.
嘿，爸爸。
- Hey. Ready to go? - Yep.
-嘿.准备好了吗，-准备好了
Uh, Mr. Batman, you have an awesome cave.
蝙蝠侠先生你有一个很棒的洞穴。
It was really great to meet you.
见到你真的很高兴。
Oh! And, uh, here.
噢!还有，呃，给你。
How did it go?
结果如何？（后来呢？）？
As well as can be expected.
正如可以预期的那样。
Mom, I met Batman!
妈妈，我见过蝙蝠侠了！
He's so...
他太..。
- Uh, broody? - No, I was gonna say cool.
-嗯，布鲁迪？-不，我是想说酷.
All right, kiddo, time for bed.
好了，孩子，该睡觉了。
But, dad, we should go on patrol, right?
但是，爸爸，我们应该去巡逻，对吗？
I mean, you never know what bad guys are up to in Smallville.
我是说，你永远不知道坏人在小镇干嘛。
Then lucky them, because you need some sleep.
那就算他们走运了，因为你需要休息。
You have school tomorrow.
你明天要上学。
I'm leaving a present on your nightstand.
我在你的床头柜上放了一件礼物。
It'll help you on your first step to being a superhero.
它将帮助你迈向成为超级英雄的第一步。
Thanks, dad.
谢谢你，爸爸。
I love you guys.
我好爱你们。
- Good night. - Love you, too.
-晚安.-我也爱你。
Good night.
晚安。
I have to go back out.
我得回去了。
Something strange is going on at the watchtower.
瞭望塔上发生了一些奇怪的事情。
- It's the night for that, I suppose. - What do you mean?
-我想，今晚是时候了。-你是什么意思？
I've been getting these wild tips
我一直在得到这些疯狂的提示
from contacts all throughout central and South America.
来自中美洲和南美洲各地的联系人。
The crime rate has plummeted.
犯罪率直线下降。
Well, that's good, right?
嗯，那很好，对吧？
You would think. But when I say "plummeted,"
你可能会想。但当我说“暴跌”时
I mean, there's no more crime.
我是说，再也没有犯罪了。
Not even a purse snatching being reported.
甚至连抢钱包的报告都没有。
We should go investigate.
我们应该去调查一下。
I'll go get my cape.
我去拿我的披风。
- We did good. - Yeah, we sure did.
-我们做得很好。-是的，我们确实是这样做的.
Watchtower. Batman, security code 0x-11 docking.
瞭望塔。蝙蝠侠，安全代码0x-11正在对接。
It's quiet.
这里很安静。
- Let's do a full sweep. - On it.
-让我们做一个全面的检查。-在这上面.
We have to get out of here. Now!
我们得离开这里。现在!
Some present.
一些礼物。
So that's why you couldn't hit anything.
这就是你什么都打不中的原因。
You're blind.
你是个盲人。
Whatever, Melvin.
管他呢，梅尔文。
Listen, can't see Kent,
听着，我看不到肯特，
I think you need to apologize for losing our game.
我想你应该为输掉我们的比赛道歉。
"Our game"? You aren't even on our team.
“我们的游戏”？你甚至都不在我们队里。
Ooh!
哦！
I could be on the team if I wanted to.
如果我想的话，我可以加入球队。
But only nerds with good grades are allowed to play, and I'm no nerd.
但只有成绩好的书呆子才能玩，我不是书呆子。
Yeah.
嗯。
Wait. I'm on the team.
等。我是球队的一员。
Shut it, Kenny. You know what?
闭嘴，肯尼。你猜怎么着？
Maybe I'll just make Jonathan here do my homework,
也许我会让乔纳森帮我做作业
and then I'll join the team and we'll never lose again.
然后我会加入球队，我们再也不会输了。
In your dreams.
在你的梦里。
Oh!
噢!
Super-strength.
超强的力量。
You okay, Melvin?
你还好吗梅尔文？
Of course I'm okay.
我当然很好。
I must have tripped.
我一定是绊倒了。
Like I said, how about an apology?
就像我说的，道歉怎么样？
Only when your mom apologizes for your face.
只有当你妈妈为你的脸道歉的时候。
Did you just... did you...
你刚才是不是..。你有没有。
You're in for it now, Kent!
你现在有麻烦了，肯特！
Do your worst, Melvin, the moron.
尽你最大的努力，梅尔文，这个笨蛋。
Who needs the teen titans?
谁还需要青少年巨人呢？
Teen titans.
青少年巨人。
Stupid name anyway.
不管怎么说，这个名字很蠢。
I'll make my own team.
我会组建我自己的团队。
Yeah, maybe we'll even lead an assault on titans tower.
是啊，也许我们甚至会领导一场对泰坦斯塔的进攻。
Show them how well we can work together.
让他们看看我们能合作得有多好。
You tried to sneak up on me?
你想偷偷靠近我？
My mother taught me how to avoid that in the crib.
我母亲在婴儿床上教我如何避免这种情况。
Father, are you, okay?
父亲，你还好吗，好吗？
What the...
这是什么.。
Father, don't make me hurt you.
父亲，别逼我伤害你。
It is time.
是时候了。
Father, please, snap out of it.
父亲，拜托，振作起来吧。
The southern hemisphere has been taken over.
南半球已经被占领。
We 7! Be at the tipping point soon,
我们7个！很快就到了临界点，
and this planet will be ours.
这个星球将是我们的。
And the others?
其他人呢？
They've been taken care of.
他们已经被照顾好了。
All threats have been infected.
所有威胁都已被感染。
- It is time. - It is time.
-是时候了。-是时候了。
They've all been infected.
他们都被感染了。
No one's left, but...
没有人离开，但是...
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
Yes, yes, I'll save him, okay?
是的，是的，我会救他的，好吗？
But only 'cause you asked.
但只是因为你问了。
Honestly, Jonathan, I expect more from you.
说实话，乔纳森，我对你的期望更高。
And I'm sure your mother and father do, too.
我相信你的父母也是如此。
- But Melvin... - You know Melvin has issues.
-但是梅尔文...-你知道梅尔文有问题.
People like that need more sympathy and Patience.
像这样的人需要更多的同情和耐心。
And maybe, if you have the heart, they deserve friendship.
也许，如果你有诚意，他们理应得到友谊。
- You're kidding me. - No, I'm not.
-你在开玩笑吧.-不，我没有.
People like Melvin, they're hurt. They lash out.
像梅尔文这样的人，他们很受伤。他们猛烈抨击。
But you take the time to get to know them,
但你要花时间去了解他们，
well, they'll be the most loyal friend you'll ever know.
他们会是你所知道的最忠诚的朋友。
Thanks, but no thanks.
谢谢，但不用了。
Just think about it.
你好好想想看。
Now, if you were any other kid, you'd be suspended.
现在，如果你是其他孩子，你会被停职。
But as it is, I put in a call to your mother and she said,
但事实是，我给你母亲打了个电话，她说，
and I quote, "I'll be there to make sure he never does that again."
我引用他的原话：“我会在那里确保他永远不会再这样做。”
I hope you learned your lesson, young man.
我希望你吸取了教训，年轻人。
Yeah, um,
是啊，嗯，
you know what, principal Cunningham, you're right, lesson learned.
你知道吗，坎宁安校长，你说得对，吸取了教训。
You really are amazing at your job.
你真的很擅长你的工作。
I promise, no more trouble from me.
我保证，不会再有我的麻烦了。
Damn, I am good at my job.
妈的，我很擅长我的工作。
Really? Isn't that a little obvious?
真的？这是不是有点太明显了？
I was actually a fan before I found out.
在我发现这件事之前，我其实是个粉丝。
You know who was my... You know what? It doesn't matter.
你知道谁是我的..。你猜怎么着？无所谓。
What are you doing here?
你在这里干嘛？
Aliens are taking over the globe.
外星人正在占领地球。
Come on, farm boy.
来吧，农场男孩。
- We've got to go save our dads. - What? How?
-我们得去救我们的爸爸们-什么？多么?
- What happened to your face? - Uh...
-你的脸怎么了？-呃...
Actually, another power kicked in today, so...
实际上，今天又来了一股力量，所以...
It was super-strength.
这是超强的表现。
But evidently, super-strength doesn't mean invulnerability to punches, so...
但显然，超强并不意味着击打无懈可击，所以...
So you punched yourself?
所以你打了自己？
Just please stay on point. What is this about aliens?
请不要拘泥于主题。外星人是怎么回事？
That's right, you're a little slow.
是的，你有点慢。
Okay, one more time. Batman showed up,
好的，再来一次。蝙蝠侠出现了，
tried to stick some parasitic organism on me.
想把一些寄生虫粘在我身上。
I saw that you were next on the list.
我看到你是名单上的下一个。
So here I am. I've just saved you. You're welcome.
所以我就来了我刚刚救了你。不用谢。
Look at this.
看看这个。
You hanging out with cosplay losers now?
你现在和角色扮演失败者混在一起了？
Oh, he hit you.
哦，他打了你。
Yeah, I did.
是的，我说了。
Should have used your heat vision, honestly.
老实说，你应该用你的热视觉。
Listen, kid, I know he's annoying, but we have no time to interact with you
听着，孩子，我知道他很烦人，但我们没时间和你互动
you'll make time.
你会腾出时间的。
Ooh.
哦.。
What did you do?
你干什么了？
Paralyzing technique I learned from my grandfather.
我从祖父那里学到的瘫痪技术。
- He should recover, in about a week. - A week?
-他应该会康复，大约一周后。-一周？
Jonathan.
乔纳森。
It's time to go home.
该回家了。
- She's compromised. - Oh, my mom never compromises.
-她妥协了.-哦，我妈妈从不妥协.
She's been taken over, idiot.
她被接管了，笨蛋。
What? No. No! She's fine.
什么？不是的。不是的！她很好。
I've been around the block, Kent.
我一直在附近转悠，肯特。
I know when someone's being mind controlled.
我知道什么时候有人被精神控制了。
- Shut up. - What, you don't believe me?
-闭嘴.-什么，你不相信我？
- Test her then. - Okay, fine.
-那就试试看.-好的，好的.
I'll test her.
我要给她做个测试。
Hi, mom. Uh...
嗨，妈妈。呃.。
When we get home, can I play video games
我们到家后，我可以玩电子游戏吗？
and maybe break into that tub of ice cream
或者闯入那桶冰激凌
you try to hide from me in the freezer?
你想躲在冰箱里躲避我吗？
Mm.
嗯。
Of course, dear. That sounds like a marvelous idea.
当然可以，亲爱的。这听起来是个绝妙的主意。
Now, come over here and give me a hug.
现在，过来给我一个拥抱。
- Yeah, she's been taken over. - Told you.
-是的，她被接管了.-告诉过你了.
Jonathan,
乔纳森
I said come over here and give me a hug.
我说过来给我一个拥抱。
It is time.
是时候了。
She's right behind us!
她就在我们后面！
Get in!
快上车！
- Do something. - I am doing something.
-做点什么。-我在做一些事情。
I'm trying to fly away.
我正试着飞走。
You do something.
你得做点什么。
You have heat vision. Just kill her already.
你有强烈的视觉。直接杀了她吧。
I am not gonna kill my mom!
我不会杀我妈妈的！
Oh, there! The pond! Can you get us over there?
哦，在那里！池塘！你能带我们去那里吗？
Sorry, mom.
对不起，妈妈。
You think she's okay?
你觉得她还好吗？
Yeah, she's fine. Greatjob.
是的，她很好。干得好。
Uh, maybe we should...
也许我们应该..。
Jonathan.
乔纳森。
We need to lay low, examine the alien for weaknesses.
我们需要保持低调，检查外星人的弱点。
And how are we going to do that? You have an alien handy?
我们将如何做到这一点？你手头有个外星人吗？
- Actually... - All right.
-事实上...-好的.
So, s.T.A.R. Labs maybe? Kord tech?
那么，也许是S.T.A.R.实验室？科德科技？
No, no. They'll be compromised.
不，不是的。他们会受到威胁的。
Okay, then where?
好吧，那在哪里？
I have an idea.
我有个主意。
Come on, lift with your knees.
来吧，用膝盖抬起。
I'm kind of new to this super-strength thing.
我对这种超强的运动还是个新手。
Just give me a minute.
给我一分钟就好。
Sure. Every minute we waste here,
好的。我们在这里浪费的每一分钟，
the world is being overrun by murderous starfish,
这个世界正在被凶残的海星肆虐，
but take your time.
不过，慢慢来。
- What? - Take your time! You're doing great!
-什么？-慢慢来！你做得很好！
Okay, okay, okay! I got it! I got it! I got it!
好吧，好吧，好吧！这样啊，原来是这么回事!这样啊，原来是这么回事!这样啊，原来是这么回事!
Yes! Oh, did you see that?
是!哦，你看到了吗？
Who's the man? I'm the man.
这个男人是谁？我就是那个男人。
Greatjob. Now you just have to turn it.
干得好。现在你只需要把它转过来。
That's it?
就这样?
My father said Superman kept his most prized possessions here.
我父亲说超人把他最珍贵的东西都放在这里。
And all it takes to get in is a large key?
只需要一把大钥匙就能进去吗？
So, I guess super-intellect is not one of his powers.
所以，我猜超级智力不是他的能力之一。
What was that?
那是什么？
Probablyjust the ice,
可能只是因为冰，
you know, melting.
你知道的，融化。
Is that a dog?
那是一只狗吗？
Your dad has a super-dog? Why didn't he tell you he has a super-dog?
你爸爸有一只超级狗？他为什么不告诉你他有一只超级狗？
Questions I'm gonna ask later.
我稍后要问的问题。
I got it!
这样啊，原来是这么回事!
Come on!
赶快!
[Yelpingi
[叶尔平吉
Which way?
哪条路？
How should I know? I've never been here before.
我怎么会知道？我以前从未来过这里。
Then why did we come here?
那我们为什么来这里？
What?
什么？
Heel!
跟上！
And I thought the batcave was weird.
我觉得蝙蝠洞很奇怪。
Krypto. Don't you know who this is?
克利普托。你不知道这是谁吗？
This is Kal-El's son, Jonathan.
这是卡尔·艾尔的儿子乔纳森。
Okay! Okay! Okay! Okay! Okay! Good boy.
好吧!好吧!好吧!好吧!好吧!真是好孩子。
How did you know who I was?
你怎么知道我是谁？
A cursory glance at your DNA.
粗略地瞥一眼你的DNA。
What are you, some kind of ghost?
你是什么人，鬼魂吗？
No. I am the artificial embodiment of Jonathan's grandfather, Jor-El.
不是的。我是乔纳森祖父乔-艾尔的人工化身。
I, along with krypto,
我和克里普托一起，
are the guardians of the fortress of solitude.
是孤独堡垒的守护者。
My grandfather?
我的祖父？
Yes. You are from along line of heroes and scientists.
是。你们来自英雄和科学家的行列。
The house of El lives in you now.
艾尔家族现在住在你的身体里。
It's important that you understand who you are and where you've come from.
重要的是，你要明白你是谁，你来自哪里。
Embedded in the crystals before you is the total accumulation
在你面前的水晶中嵌入的是总的积累
of all literature and scientific fact from dozens of other worlds
来自其他几十个世界的所有文献和科学事实
spanning the 28 known galaxies.
横跨28个已知星系。
Yeah, sorry, old timer. Maybe another time.
是啊，抱歉，老前辈。也许改天吧。
Right now, we got bigger problems.
现在，我们有更大的问题。
Is there any way you can scan this, tell us what it is?
你有没有办法扫描一下，告诉我们这是什么？
Yes, that is a spore from the alien known as starro.
是的，这是来自外星人Starro的孢子。
"Starro"?
“斯塔罗”？
A parasitic creature that can produce millions of spores.
一种能产生数百万个孢子的寄生生物。
These spores, such as you have in your vial,
这些孢子，就像你瓶子里的一样，
are then deposited onto an unsuspecting planet,
然后被存放在一个毫无戒心的星球上，
taking control of its populace,
控制着它的民众，
effectively controlling the planet
有效控制地球
until the hive mind can then drain it of life unabated.
直到蜂群的思想能够有增无减地耗尽它的生命。
"Hive mind"?
“蜂巢思维”？
Like a queen ant?
就像一只蚁后？
Similar. Yes.
差不多。是。
- What are you prattling on about? - My dad.
-你们在唠叨什么？-我爸爸.
He said that a bunch of hive-controlled insects were going crazy.
他说一群控制蜂巢的昆虫正在发疯。
They must have been reacting to the presence of the hive mind.
它们一定是对蜂群思维的出现做出了反应。
Which means, just like the queen ant,
这意味着，就像蚂蚁后一样，
if we can take out the hive mind,
如果我们能除掉蜂群思维，
- then the spores will just... - Die.
-然后孢子就会...-去死。
Huh.
哈。
Impressive.
令人印象深刻。
More iikelyjust lucky.
更像是运气好。
Mm-hmm.
嗯-嗯。
So, how do we kill it?
那么，我们要怎么杀死它呢？
Unknown.
未知。
My biological counterpart had just acquired the specimen
我的生物同行刚刚获得了这个标本
before Krypton was destroyed.
在氪被摧毁之前。
What good are you?
你有什么用处？
Can you at least tell us where this thing is?
你至少能告诉我们这东西在哪里吗？
I'm sorry. That is beyond my capability.
对不起。这超出了我的能力范围。
Great.
太棒了。
You know, my mom told me that in order to figure out a story,
你知道吗，我妈妈告诉我，为了想出一个故事，
you have to start from the beginning.
你必须从头开始。
- When did these spores start showing up? - I know this.
-这些孢子什么时候开始出现的？-我知道.
After you came to visit us at the batcave,
你来蝙蝠洞看过我们之后，
my father and your dad went to investigate
我父亲和你父亲去调查
some problem at the watchtower.
瞭望塔出了点问题。
Something had hit it the night before, knocking out their communications.
前一天晚上，有什么东西击中了它，切断了他们的通讯。
They thought it was some random space debris.
他们认为那是一些随机的太空碎片。
But odds are...
但可能性是...
- It was the hive mind! - It was the hive mind.
-是蜂群思维！-是蜂群思维
- So that means... - We have to go to space.
-所以这意味着...-我们必须去太空。
We have to go to space!
我们得去太空了！
Miss Lane! Miss Lane!
莱恩小姐！莱恩小姐！
Mr. White's been trying to get a hold of you.
怀特先生一直在找你。
Some sort of global pandemic has hit the southern states
某种全球大流行袭击了南部各州
and he wants you at the front line to...
他想让你在前线...
- Open your mouth. - What?
张开你的嘴。-什么？
Jimmy, open your mouth.
吉米，张开嘴。
- Are you okay, miss Lane? - No, none of us are.
你还好吗莱恩小姐-不好我们都不好
Jimmy, there are aliens. They reach into your...
吉米，这里有外星人。他们把手伸进你的..。
Jimmy, my son is out there.
吉米，我儿子还在外面。
I know he's in the middle of this, and I need to help him.
我知道他牵涉其中，我需要帮助他。
I thought maybe I could slip onto the mid-day program,
我想也许我可以跳上中午的节目，
warn people, but... I don't know who's been taken over.
警告人们，但是...我不知道谁被接管了。
Aliens? Well, you mean, like... You mean, like Superman?
外星人？嗯，你是说，就像……你是说，像超人那样？
No, nothing like him.
不，一点也不像他。
I think I know how to stop them, or hurt them anyway.
我想我知道如何阻止他们，或者无论如何伤害他们。
I just... we have to figure out a way to tell everyone.
我只是.。我们得想办法告诉所有人。
Get the word out.
把话传出去。
Oh. Gee, miss Lane.
噢。天哪，莱恩小姐。
The only way you could do that is if you were the president.
要做到这一点，唯一的办法就是如果你是总统。
He's allowed to break into broadcasts in the case of emergencies,
他被允许在紧急情况下闯入广播，
- but, um, seeing as how... - Jimmy, you're a genius.
-但是，嗯，看起来...-吉米，你是个天才.
Shucks, miss Lane.
天哪，莱恩小姐。
It's a little cramped.
这里有点挤。
That is because my biological counterpart
这是因为我的生物伴侣
made the ship for your father when he was but a baby.
在你父亲还是个婴儿的时候为他做了这艘船。
- I toiled for years when... - Yeah, yeah, I get it.
-我辛辛苦苦工作了很多年...-好的，好的，我明白了.
Your grandfather likes to monologue almost as much as mine.
你爷爷几乎和我爷爷一样喜欢独白。
All right, let's do this thing.
好了，我们开始吧。
Wait. There's something in my back.
等。我的背上有东西。
Sweet.
甜。
- Is that a blanket? - Not anymore.
-那是毯子吗？-不再是了.
Well, what do you think?
嗯，你觉得怎么样？
It looks... completely stupid.
它看起来..。太愚蠢了。
- Ready? - Ready.
准备好了吗-准备好了
Yes, you are right.
是的，你是对的。
Their odds of survival are not good.
他们存活的几率并不大。
Not good at all.
一点也不好。
- Whoa! - Whoa!
哇！-哇！
Where's this watchtower thing?
那个瞭望台在哪里？
Right there.
就在那里。
What if they see us?
如果他们看到我们怎么办？
Jor-El said the rocket has a built-in stealth function.
Jor-El说，火箭具有内置的隐形功能。
We shouldn't show up on any radar.
我们不应该出现在任何雷达上。
Now, with a few codes I hacked from the bat-computer...
现在，用我从蝙蝠电脑上黑下来的几个代码。
Okay, so we're just gonna go in there, and what?
好的，那我们就进去，然后呢？
What do you think? We sneak in, kill this hive mind thing
你认为如何？我们偷偷溜进去，杀了这个蜂群思维的东西
and be back for Alfred's cucumber sandwiches.
回来买艾尔弗雷德的黄瓜三明治。
Which, to be honest, are not as bad as they sound.
老实说，它们并不像听起来那么糟糕。
All right, be careful.
好的，小心点。
Careful? Please. I'm a trained assassin.
小心?请。我是个训练有素的刺客。
What? What is it?
什么？那是什么？
We're in deep...
我们陷入困境了..。
I wouldn't have come if it wasn't an emergency, Mr. President.
如果不是紧急情况，我是不会来的，总统先生。
Despite our differences, you're the only one that could help.
尽管我们有分歧，但你是唯一能帮上忙的人。
Ibeheve_.
伊贝海夫。
I know that aliens are taking over the world,
我知道外星人正在接管世界，
and I need you to make a public address warning everyone.
我需要你做一个公共演讲来警告所有人。
For you, Lois, anything.
对你来说，露易丝，什么都行。
She's clean.
她很清白。
Nothing except some hair stuff, hand sanitizer,
除了一些头发用品，洗手液，
vegan granola bar and a cigarette lighter.
素食燕麦棒和一个打火机。
I quit.
我不干了。
It's just there to remind me.
它在那里只是为了提醒我。
And I'd like to remind you
我想提醒你
that I've been saying this day would come for some time.
我一直在说这一天会到来一段时间。
You've written op-ed after op-ed about my paranoia
你写了一篇又一篇关于我妄想症的评论文章
with regards to extraterrestrials and now...
关于外星人，现在……
With regards to Superman.
关于超人。
- Listen, if you don't want... - Of course, I want to help.
-听着，如果你不想...-当然，我想帮忙。
That's all I've ever wanted to do.
这就是我一直想做的事。
But, in return...
但是，作为回报。
What?
什么？
A front page apology
头版道歉
and endorsement by you in the next election.
在下一次选举中得到你的支持。
Well, now I know you're definitely not infected.
现在我知道你肯定没有被感染。
Why is that?
为什么会这样呢？
Because you're only concerned about yourself.
因为你只关心你自己。
Do we have a deal?
我们成交了吗？
Deal.
就这么着，说好了。
Can't you, I don't know, use your heat vision or something?
你就不能，我不知道，用你的热视或别的什么吗？
Then what?
然后呢？
Silence!
安静！
You have sought to thwart my plans.
你一直试图阻挠我的计划。
But starro cannot be defeated.
但斯塔罗是不会被打败的。
It is time.
是时候了。
As long as there are free human beings, you'll never stand a chance.
只要有自由的人类，你就永远不会有机会。
You should be grateful.
你应该心存感激。
Your kind was destroying the planet.
你们这类人正在摧毁这个星球。
Now, there is no crime,
现在，没有犯罪，
no poverty, no rich, no poor,
没有贫穷，没有富人，没有穷人，
no more destruction of the environment.
不再破坏环境。
At the cost of our free will,
以我们的自由意志为代价，
and until you suck it dry for yourself.
直到你自己把它吸干。
Correct.
对，是这样。
And then I'll move to the next planet, and the next.
然后我会搬到下一个星球，然后再下一个。
With the technology that you've accumulated,
用你积累的技术，
my kind will take over the universe.
我的同类将接管整个宇宙。
And there is nothing you can do to stop it.
而你也无法阻止这一切。
Damian!
达米安！
So, what about us?
那么，我们呢？
Are we going to join your starfish-headed goons?
我们要加入你的海星头打手吗？
No, you have offended me.
不，你冒犯了我。
Kill them.
杀了他们。
Don't do this! You're heroes!
不要这样做！你们是英雄！
It's okay, Jonathan.
没关系，乔纳森。
I never liked this green cowled rip-off of my dad's anyway.
不管怎么说，我从来都不喜欢我爸爸的这种绿色套头衫。
Come on, Robin hood. I'm right here.
来吧，罗宾汉。我就在这里。
No. No, no, no, no, no.
不是的。不，不，不。
What did you do?
你干什么了？
You idiot! You can't even take a batarang.
你这个白痴！你甚至连巴塔朗都不能拿。
What makes you think... Stupid, stupid farm boy.
你怎么会觉得..。愚蠢的农场男孩。
I was just beginning to like you.
我刚刚开始喜欢上你了。
Huh. Good.
哈。好的。
- You're arrow proof? - I'm arrow proof.
-你是防箭的？-我是防箭的.
All right, justice dweebs.
好了，正义之子们。
My friend here is about to kick your ass.
我的朋友要揍你一顿了。
I am so sorry, wonder girl! I...
我很抱歉，神奇女郎！我..。
My fellow Americans...
我的美国同胞们。
We're faced with a crisis of global proportions.
我们面临着一场全球性的危机。
It's been brought to my attention
这件事引起了我的注意
that an extraterrestrial being has begun to take over our world.
一个外星生物已经开始接管我们的世界。
I urge you to remain calm
我敦促你保持冷静
and allow yourself to be taken
并允许你自己被带走
by the almighty starro.
被全能的斯塔罗。
It is time.
是时候了。
It's time for you to burn, you son of a bitch!
该烧死你了，你这个狗娘养的！
Mom?
妈妈?
I'm an investigative reporter, asshole.
我是个调查记者，混蛋。
I knew you were taken over the minute you took the meeting.
从你开会的那一刻起，我就知道你被接管了。
Jonathan, I know you're out there.
乔纳森，我知道你还在外面。
I'm hoping, praying you can see this.
我希望，祈祷你能看到这一切。
Heat can hurt this thing. You hear me, Jonathan Kent?
高温会伤害这玩意儿。听到了吗，乔纳森·肯特？
Burn this mother...
烧了这个母亲..。
Mom, mom!
妈妈，妈妈！
Okay, so it doesn't like heat.
好的，所以它不喜欢热。
This is too easy.
这太容易了。
About time.
时间差不多了。
Yeah, well, I was busy.
是啊，我当时很忙。
Turns out the hive mind isn't a fan of heat.
事实证明，蜂群思维并不是热度的粉丝。
It won't come off.
它脱不下来。
Even with super strength.
即使拥有超强的体力。
Then we need to take out the hive mind.
那我们就得干掉蜂群思维。
Maybe your heat vision could kill him.
也许你的热视能杀了他。
Come on, let's go.
来吧，我们走。
Gotcha!
抓到你了！
I will kill you, father.
我要杀了你，神父。
We need a new angle.
我们需要一个新的视角。
Angle. "Try a different angle." Mom was right!
角度。“试着换个角度看。”妈妈是对的！
What if we trade partners?
如果我们交换伙伴呢？
Yeah, why not?
是啊，有何不可？
But first, I'll need something.
但首先，我需要一些东西。
Help me tackle Batman.
帮我对付蝙蝠侠。
That's okay. I got it.
那好吧。这样啊，原来是这么回事。
What's that?
那是什么？
My dad's insurance policy.
我爸爸的保险单。
Whoa!
哇哦！
Man of steel?
钢铁人？
I just knocked out Batman with one punch!
我一拳就把蝙蝠侠打倒了！
It is too late.
现在已经太晚了。
We are past the tipping point.
我们已经过了临界点。
Your world is mine.
你的世界是我的。
That's what you think. Torch this thing, farm boy.
那是你自己的想法。烧了这玩意儿，农场小子。
Useless.
没用。
I don't think your heat vision's gonna cut it.
我不认为你的热视会影响到它。
Yeah, I know, but I had to try.
是啊，我知道，但我必须试一试。
- What now? - Only one thing I can think of.
-现在怎么办？-我只能想到一件事.
Yeah.
嗯。
Okay. That's everyone that could fit. Jon?
好吧。这就是所有能装得下的人。琼恩?
Sorry, dad.
抱歉，爸爸。
Ready.
准备好的。
We just have to make it to the control center
我们只要到控制中心就行了
and then drop this thing in the atmosphere.
然后把这个东西扔到大气层里。
While avoiding a malevolent hive mind that wants us dead.
同时避开想要我们死的恶毒的蜂群思维。
And that.
还有那个。
You know, my dad said being a hero was about sacrifice.
你知道吗，我爸爸说当英雄就是牺牲。
And I don't think I believed him.
我不认为我相信了他。
But now?
但现在呢？
The world needs Superman and Batman a lot more than it needs
这个世界对超人和蝙蝠侠的需求远远超过对他们的需求
a farm boy from Kansas.
一个来自堪萨斯州的农场男孩。
Or an assassin with a cow.
或者是一个带着牛的刺客。
I don't know. He's pretty cool.
我不知道。他很酷。
- Ready? - Yeah, I am.
-准备好了吗？-是的，准备好了
So, how do we knock this thing out of orbit?
那么，我们怎么才能让它脱离轨道呢？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I got it!
这样啊，原来是这么回事!
Damian!
达米安！
- Shoot it! - What if I hit you?
-开枪！-如果我打到你怎么办？
It's better than being eaten by this thing! Shoot it now!
总比被这东西吃掉要好！现在就开枪！
No! You will not stop me!
不是的！你阻止不了我！
It is my time! My time!
这是我的时代！我的时间！
Hold on!
等一等!
I can't!
我做不到!
Hold on!
等一等!
No way!
不行!
The hive mind must be losing its power.
蜂群思维肯定正在失去它的力量。
The boys!
孩子们！
- Thanks. - Don't mention it.
-谢谢.-别客气。
You know, of all the ways to go, definitely didn't see this one coming.
你知道，在所有要走的路中，肯定没有预料到这一次。
Ninjas, yes.
忍者，是的。
Joker, possibly.
可能是小丑。
Crashing to earth on a satellite while fighting off parasitic aliens,
在击退寄生的外星人时乘坐卫星坠落到地球上，
not really on my radar.
在我的雷达上没有。
Nice to know you can be surprised.
很高兴知道你会很惊讶。
Woo-hoo-hoo!
哇-呼-呼！
You're all right!
你没事了！
I'm better than all right, now that I know you're safe.
我好多了，现在我知道你安全了。
I, uh...
我，呃...
I was... worried.
我是在..。忧心忡忡。
Why? I learned from the best.
为什么？我从最好的人那里学到了东西。
I'm proud of you, Jonathan.
我为你骄傲，乔纳森。
You put the world, us, above yourself.
你把世界，我们，置于你自己之上。
That's what a hero does.
这就是英雄该做的。
That's what a Superman does.
这就是超人该做的。
I have survived the ravages of space!
我在太空的蹂躏中幸存了下来！
Did you think you could destroy me?
你以为你能毁了我吗？
You are nothing.
你什么都不是。
You are...
你是..。
Jonathan, get ready!
乔纳森，准备好！
I'd call that a home run.
我会把这叫做本垒打。
Hey, Damian. Listen, we took another vote.
嘿，达米安。听着，我们又投了一票。
- You did? - Yes.
-是吗？-是的
After what you did on the watchtower,
在你在瞭望塔上做了那些事之后，
- saving us... - And the world.
-拯救我们...-和世界。
And the world,
而这个世界，
we'd be honored if you joined the titans.
如果你加入泰坦队，我们会很荣幸。
Did we get cut off?
我们被切断了吗？
Damian, can you hear me?
达米安，你能听到我说话吗？
Oh, uh, I heard you. But you know what? Uh, I have a prior engagement.
哦，呃，我听到了。但是你知道吗？呃，我已经有约了。
Let me get back to you on that.
关于这一点，我再给你回电话。
Get back to me on...
给我回电话……
You're enjoying this a bit too much.
你有点太享受这个了。
It's the little things.
都是些小事。
Come on. I don't want to be late. Never been to a baseball game before.
赶快。我不想迟到。我以前从来没看过棒球比赛。
Now batting, Jonathan Kent.
现在击球，乔纳森·肯特。
Good luck, can't hit...
祝你好运，打不中..。
Knock 'em dead, kiddo!
打倒他们吧，孩子！
- I thought you had an emergency. - Barry's handling it.
-我以为你有急事。-巴里在处理.
Besides, I have more important things to take care of.
另外，我还有更重要的事情要处理。
Hit it like it's an extraterrestrial parasitic monster!
就像它是外星寄生怪物一样打击它！
Go, go, go! Good job, Jonathan.
快，快，快！干得好，乔纳森。
- You got it, buddy! - Good job!
-你做到了，伙计！-干得好！
Keep going!
继续往前走！
So, what now?
那么，现在怎么办？
You think we should join the teen titans?
你觉得我们应该加入青少年巨人队吗？
Go on patrol?
去巡逻吗？
I mean, what's next for the new dynamic duo?
我的意思是，新的活力二人组的下一步是什么？
Nope. Dynamic duo is Batman and Robin.
不是的。动态二人组是蝙蝠侠和罗宾。
We're super sons.
我们是超级儿子。
Okay. Fine.
好吧。很好。
What's next for the super sons?
超级儿子们的下一步是什么？
Well, I do owe you a birthday present.
嗯，我确实欠你一份生日礼物。
Well, what is it?
好吧，那是什么？
This.
这。
Still can't fly.
还是不能飞。